<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright 2018 BloomReach Inc. (http://www.bloomreach.com)

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the  "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS"
    BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.
-->

<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Configuration</title>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <section name="Configuration">
      <subsection name="General">
        <p>This addon employs a number of modules to perform its operations:
          <ul>
            <li>
              <p>Archive manager: the module that connects to an external archiving agency and requests an archiving operation</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Updates jobs manager: this module creates WebArchiveUpdate jobs in a queue implemented via a JCR dedicated node structure</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Updates processor: An implementation of org.onehippo.repository.scheduling.RepositoryJob that consumes the WebArchive updates from the queue</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>SCXML action: an action registered for both publication and depublication of documents</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>Channel publication listener: registered when a channel is published or taken offline</p>
            </li>
            <li>
              <p>HST URL service: retrieves all URLs for a document that was published or was taken offline</p>
            </li>
          </ul>
          <p>These modules are initialised by a daemon module (org.bloomreach.forge.webarchiving.cms.WebArchivingServicesDaemonModule)</p>
        </p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="Archive manager">
        <p>The most important configuration is about selecting the Web Archive manager to be used. This is governed by dependency management in your pom,
          please see <a href="install.html">install page</a>.</p>
        <p>Depending on the manager used, different parameters will be exposed. The configuration can be found under
          /hippo:configuration/hippo:modules/web-archiving-addon-services-daemon/archivemanager</p>
        <p>
          For maintainability reasons, the api request format as well as the credentials needed for using the service are configurable under: /hippo:configuration/hippo:modules/crispregistry/hippo:moduleconfig/crisp:resourceresolvercontainer/archiefWebEndpoint
          and the location mentioned above</p>
      </subsection>

      <subsection name="HST URL service">
        <p>Configuration for this service can be found under /hippo:configuration/hippo:modules/web-archiving-addon-services-daemon/hsturlservice.
          The service uses a specific host group as registered in hst:hosts. The name of the desired host group to use needs to be configured in the location above.</p>
      </subsection>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
